Jon Nielsen

Email: jon-nielsen@hotmail.com | Phone: 251952459632

Address: Bole Rwanda, Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Region, Ethiopia

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonnielsen1/ | Website: nan

Date of Birth: 1988-06-18 00:00:00 | Gender: Male | Nationality: Danish

Profile Summary

I am a versatile economist striving to use economic analysis to the benefit of the least advantaged. I have extensive experience in doing macroeconomic model calculations, data analyses and literature reviews, and in presenting my findings in a non-technical way. Further, I have experience as team leader, coordinator and project manager.

Work Experience

Head of Section at Ministry of Finance of Denmark (2015-08-25 00:00:00 - 2017-06-07 00:00:00)

Location: Copenhagen, Denmark

Responsibilities:

Chief Analyst at Economic Council of The Labour Movement (2017-06-08 00:00:00 - 2024-05-31 00:00:00)

Location: Copenhagen, Denmark

Responsibilities: Economic analyses

Education

Master's Degree in Economics

Institution: University of Cambridge | Dates: 2014-08-31 00:00:00 - 2017-06-07 00:00:00

Location: Cambridge, United Kingdom

Skills & Tools

Languages

English